-=耐卡影音论坛出品=-由零点字幕组翻译 更多精彩美剧请登录www.ncar.cc/bbs欣赏
Your credit based on several factors.
信用额度取决于几个因素
After listening to your story ...
在听了你的故事之后...
- ... Sorry, your credit is denied. - Rejected?
-...对不起 你的申请失败 -被拒绝？
- You're fooling us! - There must be a mistake.
-你在耍我们  -肯定是哪里搞错了
I have a document that shows my payments smoothly.
我有文件能证明我没有延迟任何付款
I understand, Mr. Vega, but as I said, there are other factors.
我理解的 维加先生 但就如我所说的 决定因素不只一个
You've been on the verge of a credit line is drawn.
您的信用额度是处于最低值得
Look, Mr. Guillermo Gomez.
听着 吉列莫·戈麦斯先生
My friend Bernie had heart surgery twice for six months.
我朋友伯尼六个月内进行了两次心脏手术
We have ...
我们还...
We have 10 recipes for drinking ...
我们每两星期...
... Every two weeks.
要喝10种类型的酒...
Do not anyone move!
所有人 不准动！
Listen! I want all of them lie down on the floor!
听着 所有人给我趴到地上
Do not try to do desperate!
别想着做些愚蠢的事
And you, old man!
而你 老头
Be careful, Frank.
小心点 弗兰克
- Why do you act recklessly? - I'm sorry, Bernie, was not accidental.
-你为什么这么不知死活？ -对不起 伯尼 这不是偶然
Hey, what are you doing?
嘿 你在干嘛
Because I have to spend $ 199 to make up for this boring recipe.
因为我不得不花199刀来维持这无聊的食谱
It was only $ 190, right? Just so you know ...
只有190刀吧？你知道的...
... The drug is purchased from money pensiunanku!
这些药是从
You just talk to me now that the drug is purchased from pensiunanmu, huh?
你刚才说这些药是从
No no. Only to turn when someone comes to stir.
不不 别哪壶不开提哪壶
- You ungrateful, jerk? - You're a jerk!
-你不知感恩 混蛋 -你这个混蛋
You've made a mistake, asshole.
你犯了大错了 混蛋
Everybody down!
所有人 趴下
This is great!
真好
Only by using a chair and a baseball bat ...
只用了一把椅子和球棒...
Two parents ...
两对父母...
... Managed to thwart the robbery.
想要阻止这场抢劫
Is Bank provides loans as a token of gratitude?
银行是否为了表示谢意才给你们提供贷款？
No. But they gave us something else.
不是 他们给了我们其他的东西
Certificates of appreciation.
一份荣誉证书
See, this is cool!
看 多酷 啊
Look at us, pal. Greater than Vin Diesel.
看看我们 爸爸 这比冯·迪索还赞
Nonsense!
放屁
- Who is it? - Rosario.
-这是谁 -罗萨里奥
- What is he now in Arizona? - Florida.
-他在亚利桑那州干嘛 -他是在佛罗里达
The, the ... dia ..
这..这...
- ... He is fine. - I'm sorry, friend.
-...他挺好的 -抱歉 兄弟
No, no. Everything is fine.
不 不 一切都挺好的
I'm happy for him.
我为他而高兴
Rosario had a good job.
罗萨里奥找到一份好工作了
Julie get into a good school. I'm happy for them.
朱丽进了一所好学校 我为他们高兴
- Hello? - You want to avoid me? All Right.
-哈罗？ -你想避开我么 好吧
Cursed if you're not the most difficult to find.
如果我找到你 我一定会诅咒的
Carmen, my love, what happened?
卡门 亲爱的 你怎么了
Nothing special, except the fact that I'm getting married!
除了我即将结婚 也没什么特别的
What?
什么？
By Jeffrey. We met six weeks ago.
新郎是杰弗瑞 我们认识了六个星期
Approaches such as molasses and pie.
但是就像是蜜糖和派般分不开
I've never been tied like that, Frank.
我从未感受到如此紧密的联系 弗兰克
This is good news! I can not wait to meet you!
这是个好消息 我等不及要见你们了
- There is free time this weekend! - Oh yeah?
-我们这个星期有空 -真的么
Yes I Do! I want you to be present in the wedding!
是的 我们希望你能出席婚礼
Gather your belongings. Come!
收拾你的行李 来吧
Carmen, very good!
卡门 这很好
We wanted to come, but ...
我们也想去 但...
I and Bernie now has financial problems.
我和伯尼经济出了点状况
Shut up, Franklin.
闭嘴 弗兰克
Your basis miser, always a lot of reasons.
你这吝啬鬼 总是有很多借口
Not that forget the goodness of your father, but ...
不要忘了你老爸的好 但是...
There are no buts, Vega. Already booked your flight schedule.
没有但是 维加 我们已经帮你买好机票
Already paid for your vacation.
这一趟由我们出钱
So, prepare your bags and come here.
所以 赶紧收拾你的行李 来吧
Before I came and dragged yourself.
在我飞过去 把你抗过来之前
Pal ...
爸爸...
... This garbage does not fit with my stomach.
这东西很难吃
Why did not want to eat fish on the plane? Throw it!
在飞机上不想吃鱼么 扔了它
I'm going to the toilet.
我去趟厕所
Son of a bitch.
混蛋
Hello, Miss.
嘿 小姐
What do you have for dessert?
您想吃什么甜点
Still getting used to, I do not have time for a relationship.
我还没缓过来 也没时间交朋友
But I had time for one night.
可是我一整晚都有时间耶
- Do you agree with such an experience? - One night ...
-你想试试看么 -一晚
... Two nights ... As it should be.
按理说...两晚
Excuse me, sir.
不好意思 先生
You should go back to your seat.
请回您的座位去
This is my new place.
这是我的新座位
Can I see your ticket?
我能看下您的票么
Come on, let alone me.
好了 让我一人静静
It's my pleasure.
当然
Son of a bitch.
混蛋
The passengers and gentlemen, we will land in Baton Rouge.
各位乘客 我们即将降落巴吞鲁日
The time is now 15:00 and the temperature is 18 degrees.
现在的时间是下午三点 室外温度是18度
I forget the smell of the south side.
我已经忘了南部的气味了
- Yes I Do! - What is it us?
-我也是 -我们是谁？
I do not think there are other names such as Vega in Louisiana.
除了路易桑那州的维加 我想不出还能叫什么名字
Gentlemen, my name is Khan. Can I carry your bag?
先生 我是可汗 我能帮您拿包么
- I can take it alone. - I insisted.
-我能自己拿 -请让我为您拿包
Hell, you can take my bag.
见鬼了 那你就拿吧
Please, gentlemen.
是的 先生
We have to get used to.
我们要学着适应
Oh, come on!
噢 走吧
oh crap!
哦糟糕
- Give me the bag! - Fuck you!
-给我袋子 -艹
Did you like it, asshole?
你喜欢这样么 混蛋
I'll take care of this.
我会看好的
You're quite large in Ventruz.
你还真是挺大只的
Okay, okay.
好 好
Son of a bitch!
混蛋
I will kill you!
我会杀了你的
Nose ... you broke my nose!
鼻子...你打断我的鼻子
- It's your bag, baby. - Thank you.
-这是你的袋子 宝贝 -谢谢
Have a nice day.
祝你愉快
- Her parents live here? - Yes sir.
-她的父母住在这？ -是的
Finally able to start a party!
终于能开趴了
- You look great! - Now I have a chance, man.
-你看起来很好 -我现在有一个机会 兄弟
I no longer singles!
我不再是一个人了
Come on, you'll meet my parents.
来 见见我的父母
Unfortunately, if I know you have a lot of money, I could ask him six months ago.
不幸的是 如果我知道你这么有钱 我肯定早就跟他求婚了
Mom, dad, I introduced Frank and Bernie.
妈 爸 这是弗兰克和伯尼
Welcome, gentlemen. It's nice to meet you.
欢迎 先生们 很高兴见到你们
- Thank you for the welcome. - You're so good-natured.
-谢谢您的邀请 -你真是太好心了
- The pleasure is ours. - Carmen, say that they are so good.
-这是我们的荣幸 -卡门也说他们很好人
Calm down, Miss.
冷静点 小姐
Hey, you guys.
嘿 伙计
Oh God, what's going on!
哦我的天 发生什么了
Kyle and his friends.
卡尔和他的朋友们
Earl, you see? / That's just a scratch. It's okay, he will be fine.
厄尔 看到了么 这只是抓伤而已 没事 很快会好的
They are friends brother from California. Bernie and Frank.
他们是从加利福尼亚过来的两兄弟伯尼和弗兰克
- Hello? - Do you?
-哈罗 -你是？
Yes, he's my brother from another mother.
是的 他是我同父异母的兄弟
My mother was pregnant with tubes. I think sperm confused.
我妈妈去做了试管受孕 我觉得惨的是精子
For me it is the same.
对我来说都是一样的
Anyway we love Ronnie!
不管怎么说 我们爱罗尼
Welcome and I'll show you to your room.
欢迎 我带你们去房间
Gosh, Earl!
天哪 厄尔
- This house seems well organized! - Not so need a big cost.
-这间屋子看来管理得当 -不用花很多钱
- How so? - This family of hereditary property.
-为什么 -这是我们家的财产
Heritage house my great-grandfather, because of his service in the war.
因为我的外祖父曾在军中服役 所以政府给我们这座房子
As part of the fund negro farmers.
作为黑人农民基金会的一部分
Really nobody knew this house was built.
没人知道我们建了这间屋子
Mineral resources, including oil,
矿产资源 包括油
- ... Make us a millionaire. - Damn!
-...让我们成为了百万富翁 -该死的
- Karma which "sucks!" - It is true.
-烂透了的罪恶 -确实
I hope you do not mind sleeping in one room.
我希望你们不介意在这个房间里休息
We will have a lot of guests and the house is definitely full.
我们的客人太多 客房都满了
- I do not know you're retired. - Oh, yes ...
-我不知道你已经退休了 -哦 是的
I spent some time. Many years ago.
我已经退休很久了
Do not even know who I am.
甚至连自己是谁都快不知道
It seems that everything is here, but if you need anything else ...
所有的用品这里都用 如果你还需要其他什么东西...
- ... Do not hesitate to ask. - I would be sent "chick"?
-请告诉我 不用犹豫 -有特殊服务么
- After midnight. - Why so late?
-要午夜过后才有 -为什么这么晚
Buddy, I want to thank you.
哥们 我想谢谢你
For taking care of my girls, when in LA.
在洛杉矶的时候那么照顾我女儿
- He was very meaningful to me. - Carmen is very special.
-他对我意义非凡 -卡门是个特别的人
Oh no!
噢不
Afternoon workout in one hour, you have to get dressed!
下午一个小时之内 你必须打扮好
I keep a couple of coats in the closet for you.
衣橱有几件外套
I think according to your size.
应该合你的尺寸
Let's get there!
走吧
- The whole country is here! - You can see it.
-整个城市就在这里 -你能看得到的
Gentlemen, I offer some of the best drinks in Louisiana?
先生们 我能为你们提供一些路易桑那州最好的酒么
Of course!
当然
Wow, I have never seen a plant drinks.
哇 我从没见过植物饮料
This is not a plant, lord, this Mid Sprigs.
这不是植物 先生 这是仲春
Really refreshing!
好新鲜
Hope you enjoy!
希望你们喜欢
- Mid Sprigs...
- Kita tos!
-仲春... -基塔·陶斯
As seen in the magazine!
在杂志上看到过的
You're the old farts are awesome!
你真是太迷人了
Here it is! I can not leave it for a while without someone seduce.
我来了 要是没有某人的劝说 我还脱不开身呢
Oh dear, meet Frank and Bernie.
亲爱的 来见见弗兰克和伯尼
Jeffreyku Recommend this!
杰弗瑞推荐的
Gentlemen, an honor to meet you. You Frank, right?
先生们 很荣幸见到你们 弗兰克 是么
- Nice to meet you. - And you, definitely "Green Machine".
-很高兴见到你 -你一定是“绿色机器”了
Yes, nice to meet you. I said congratulations!
是的 很高兴见到你 恭喜了
- Thank you sir. - You found an amazing woman!
-谢谢 -你拥有了一个完美的女人
I know that. I am blessed!
我知道 我很幸运
I certainly good in a past life, it was worth it.
我前世修来的福 太值得了
Is not that funny?
是不是很有趣
Jeffrey!
杰弗瑞
It seems that someone called me.
有人在喊我
Excuse me, gentlemen.
抱歉 先生们
Dear?
亲爱的？
A great guy!
真是个棒小伙
I never felt like it! Make me happy!
我从未有过这样的感受 我很开心
What happened to him?
他怎么了
- Sorry, I ask it. - He had an accident in Afghanistan.
-对不起 是我问的 -他在阿富汗出了意外
- It happened when he save his friend. - I am sorry.
-他救他朋友的时候 自己出了事 -对不起
It is okay.
没事
Will I lead the life of a three-meter.
今后我的生活会只剩下三米么
Thanks to everyone for coming. Now I want to make a speech a little.
谢谢大家的到来 我想作个小小的演讲
It's hard for a father to see his daughter grow up ...
对于一个父亲来说 看着自己的女儿长大
... And then give it to a stranger.
然后嫁给一个陌生人 是一件痛苦的事
Wait!
等等
This is my first wedding speech text.
错了 这是我第一次写的婚礼致辞
Here it is! It is hard for a father ...
啊 这才是！对于一个父亲来说
... To see his daughter grow up ...
看着自己的女儿长大
... And give it to strangers.
然后嫁给一个陌生人 是一件痛苦的事
Took it, and then give them back.
带走他们 然后又归还
But it was quieter when her husband-a man like Jeffrey.
当她的丈夫是像杰弗瑞这样的人 一切又似乎平静的多
Your mother and I hope you get the best!
你的妈妈和我希望你得到最好
- Now we are toast! - Yes I Do.
-让我们拿起酒杯 -我愿意
Unfortunately, I wish you all the best in the world forever!
不幸的是 我希望你们的未来一切顺利
Always keep happiness, love ...
永远快乐 爱情永在
... And you know the next.
然后 你知道的
- Leave him! - Shut up!
-离他远点 -闭嘴
Bernie!
伯尼
God, Bernie, help me!
天哪 伯尼 帮帮我
Frank?
弗兰克？
Frank!
Damn!
该死的
How can you sleep at a time like this?
你怎么能睡成这样
Where is Carmen?
卡门在哪
I'll tell you.
我等下告诉你
Carmen was kidnapped!
卡门被绑架了
I do not know, I was sleeping ...
我不知道 我正在睡觉
... And then some people came and took him.
有人冲进来 带走了他
I only remember up there. Damn, what you do not look for it?
我只记得这些 该死的 你怎么不把他找回来
Relax, this is part of the procedure.
放轻松 这是计划的一部分
You do not understand! They kidnapped my fiance!
你不明白 他们绑架了我的未婚妻
Shit. We do not hear anything, while Frank screaming.
该死的 弗兰克叫喊的时候 我们根本没听到
- When we arrived, they were gone. - I'm worried about my son!
-我们到的时候他们已经走了 -我很担心我的儿子
Can you give evidence?
你有什么线索么
I do not see much in the dark.
当时太黑了 我看不见
They have a ski mask ...
他们带着滑雪面具
- They are quite a lot. - How many are they?
-他们训练有素 -他们有多少人
- Eight ... ten. Probably more. - How do you not know?
-八...十 或是更多 -你怎么可能不知道
Perhaps because the prison is full.
可能是因为当时房间里太多人了
- They attacked me and nobody helped me! - Now you blame me?
-他们袭击我而你们没一个人出来帮我 -现在反倒来责怪我？
Gentlemen!
先生
It would help us to restore it.
这有助于我们找回她
You must find her. The town is small.
你必须找到她 这个城市不大
239 139 people, exactly, Mr. Vega.
维加先生 准确来说 是239139个人
- Maybe a little more. - Sir, I think my job ends here.
-可能还要多一旦 -先生 我想我的任务完成了
We form a team.
我们要建一支队伍
Post a surveillance camera.
查看监视器
I do not want to just wait for news wayangku mere child.
我不想只是在这等着坏消息
I do not care how much money you took out.
我不在乎你花多少钱
You have to restore my son now.
你必须把我女儿带回来
- Now the time is not right. - Someone called about Carmen.
-这不是最佳时间 -有人打电话找卡门
- Did he call? - Yes I Do.
-是他么 -是的
Give me the phone.
给我电话
Without offering, Mr. Morgan. Five million for your daughter.
摩根先生 废话不多说 拿五百万来换你女儿
You've got 32 hours, waiting for the phone again to meet at the location of the meeting.
给你32小时 我会再电话通知你见面的地点
If you do not follow my instructions. Your daughter is going to die.
如果不照我说的做 就等着见你女儿的尸体吧
I do not know, maybe. Black money is not good publicity.
或许 黑钱不太好见光的吧
Whoever did it, it's all been planned.
不管是谁做的 这都是计划好的
What do you feel have enemies? Or could they know you?
你有什么敌人么 他们知道你的事么
Of course, someone constantly makes investing or selling a house.
当然 那些不断在评估或售卖房子的人
I do not believe this is happening.
我不敢相信真的发生了这样的事
He's my little girl! Must be married on Sunday!
她是我的宝贝女 本该在这个星期天结婚
You can help us.
你能帮我们的
The town is small, there is rarely a crime like this.
这个小城市 很少发生这样的抢劫案的
And I know that you have experience in LA.
而且我知道是曾是个纽约警察
- Not really. - You can help us find him.
-不完全是 -你能帮我们找到她的
- Ny. Morgan, the police have been doing. - They will not do anything!
-摩根 纽约警察不是经常接这种案子么 -他们什么也不会做
Their heads are so immersed in the judge that they could not see anything.
他们如此沉迷在自己的判断里 以致他们什么都看不到
We need your help.
我们需要你的帮助
I hope you can bring Carmen home!
我希望你能带卡门回来
Hey! Look what I found at the gate.
嘿 看看我在门口找到什么
Buford? Anggota The Rouge Club?
布福德？胭脂俱乐部
Ronald found at the northern gate.
雷纳德在北门找到的
We may never know. I never liked the club.
我们可能永远不会知道 我一直不喜欢这个俱乐部
We'll check it out. Might be found instructions. Thank you, gentlemen.
我们会查清楚的 可能会发现线索的 谢谢你 先生
You know who did it, right?
你知道是谁做的 是么
I'll tell you something.
我告诉你
This is not Los Angeles.
这里不是洛杉矶
This Baton Rouge.
这里是巴吞鲁日
We do not work like the way you there.
我们的工作方式跟你不同
If you think going to intervene in this case, ..
如果你想插手这个案子
... Even a little, ..
...就算只有一分一毫...
... I'll lock you up and will not let go.
我会把你拷起来 永远关起来
Enjoy the rest of your day course.
好好享受你的余生吧
Let us catch this bastard.
把这个混蛋抓回来吧
片源:涵 听译:媛 组幕字点零
Let me be clear, now ...
让我说的清楚点 现在...
- ... Without running. - What Are?
-...不要跑 -什么
Nobody would beat each other.
不要互相干架
But I'm not going with the people.
我不会跟他们走的
You're so whiny!
你太啰嗦了
We are no longer in LA.
我们不再在洛杉矶了
26 hours 32 minutes
26小时32分
Damn chair "bite" my ass!
该死的椅子把我屁屁夹住了
Destroyed piece by piece.
把它打成渣
The good news is that my cock is still here.
好消息是我的鸟还在
Hello, Miss!
嗨 小姐们
Come On.
来吧
The last time I saw a bunch of white people amongst blacks.
最后一次看一堆白人在一圈黑人中间
Bernie, you'd better get out of the routine.
伯尼 你最好别再做这些事了
- Meet new people. - But not the kind of people like this.
-见见新朋友啊 -但不是这样的朋友
But on the other hand, my mother told me, I do not really closed.
换个角度说 我妈妈告诉我 我并不亲切待人
Hello, master and mistress!
哈罗 主人和女主人
We would like to ask.
我们想问个问题
Giliranmu, Frank.
吉列兰姆 弗兰克
I'm looking for Mr. Buford. What any of you who know him?
我在找布福德先生 你们谁知道他
I know!
我知道
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
嘿 你怎么样 兄弟
- We see you're very friendly. - Yes, you look very friendly.
-我们觉得你很友好 -是的 你看起来很友好
Stay on the floor.
呆在这里
Die, motherfucker!
该死的 混蛋
Now, I ask again!
现在 我再问一遍
Where Buford?
布福德在哪
I see you do not want it.
我想你不想要这个吧
Mr. Buford! Nice to meet you.
布福德先生 很高兴见到你
Why do not you have a VIP card?
你怎么不拿张VIP卡呢
- Where is Carmen? - Fuck!
-卡门在哪 -艹
Okay, then.
好 好
Ah ... ah ... sit back.
哈 坐回去
I do not know! I swear!
我不知道 我发誓
I had access inside.
不过我知道
Landry's Loft!
兰德里的阁楼在哪里
- Where was Landry's Loft? - In the city.
-阁楼在哪里 -在这个城市里
7th Street. The place is easy to find.
第七大街 这个地方很容易找
Thank you for your cooperation.
谢谢你的配合
Ronnie? How are you, friend?
罗尼？你怎么样 我的朋友
- I'm going to be late. - I understand.
-我可能会迟点到 -我明白
Busy people. Many activities.
大忙人 很多活动
I could see.
我了解
I ask for your help as a friend. My car was in the garage.
我以朋友的身份想请你帮忙 我的车在车库里
So, can I borrow your car this week. How Do?
所以我能借你的车用一个星期么
My car?
我的车？
This week ...
这个星期...
... Our brothers will come and I have to pick them up.
我哥要来 然后我要去接她
Oh yes, I understand.
哦是的 我明白
Listen, you lend your car or I destroy.
听着 把车借我 或者是我砸了它
You just select.
你自己选吧
Hey ... what are you supposed to be somewhere else?
嘿...你要去哪里？
- Yes, we got lost. - Go.
-是的 我们走丢了 -好吧
If you do not want to let me go, I do not want anything from you.
如果你不我走 我不会奢求你什么东西的
So, you want to hold the host?
所以 你想成为主人？
We take your shoes, let your feet cold.
我们拿走你的鞋 让你的脚变冷
Listen to me now, weirdo.
听着 呆子
If you can get away ... do you think you made a mistake.
如果你能跑掉 你会觉得这是个错误的选择么
Okay, then.
好吧
Please take your food.
吃点东西吧
Old fart damn catch Buford.
老家伙抓到布福德了
- Can you come out for a while? - Yes I Do.
-你能出来一下么 -好
How can you not able to stalk the old fart?
你怎么会把老家伙跟丢了
- I do not know what happened. - I told them not to screw up.
-我不知道发生了什么 -我告诉他们别搞砸了
20 hours 16 minutes
20小时16分
Why I'm always one to get good seats?
为什么我总是那个坐在好位置上的人
The same reasoning to sit next to a beautiful woman.
而且还总是有美女相伴
What are you talking about? Not all women are beautiful.
你在说什么 不是所有的女人都是漂亮的
Hello, Miss. We want to meet Landry.
哈罗 小姐 我们想见见兰德里
- Does he live here? - He does not live here anymore.
-他住在这么 他已经搬走了
So, off you go.
所以 请走吧
Can you tell us, where can I find it?
你能告诉我们去哪能找到他么
- Get rid of your feet from the door. - Come on, lady ...
-把你的臭脚拿开 -说吧 小姐
You do not have to ...
你不用...
- I thought he would not attack. - Hold On!
-我觉得他不会攻击的 -坚持住
Needless to violence, we just want to talk.
没必要用暴力啦 我们只是想跟你谈谈而已
We are men who can not hit a woman.
我们不是那种会打女人的男人啦
- Now tell us, where Landry! - Fuck!
-现在跟我们说吧 兰德里在哪
Let go of me!
离我远点
Not until you tell me where Landry!
只要你告诉我兰德里在哪
- Where is he? - Working in Bakets.
-他在哪 -他在贝克斯那里工作
Place for barbecue outside the city.
城外的烧烤店
Usually there in the morning. Now you get out of here!
早上通常在那 现在你们可以走了
Give up so quickly? I thought we could talk.
这么快就放弃？我还以为我们能再谈谈呢
Besides you kicked me in the ribs.
你踢了我的肋骨啊
Nose bleed?
鼻子流血了？
How are you, friend? I'm glad to find you.
怎么样了 很高兴找到你
Look, Kyle ...
看 卡尔
I need 20 bucks.
我需要20美分
- I do not have. - I thought you had.
-我没有 -我以为你有
No, really. I do not have.
不 真的 我没有钱
Give! Before I hit you.
给我 在我打你之前
Yes alright.
好吧
Why do not you get a job?
你怎么不去工作
- Who are you? - Friends of Ronald.
-你是谁 -罗纳德的朋友
I think you need to look for work.
我认为你该去找份工作
You complain to the grandparents, to protect you?
你向祖父母抱怨 让他们来保护你？
Should not you have someone to take care of you?
你难道不需要有人照顾么
I suggest you get out now, before ...
我劝你离开 在...
- Kyle! - What Are?
-卡尔 -什么
They are the one.
他们是一伙的
- What Are? - The bank robbery.
-什么 -银行抢劫案
- Damn! Wow, we are fans of yours! - Kyle?
-该死的 哇 我们是你的粉丝 -卡尔
- Dad! - What is going on here?
-爸爸 -发生什么事了
No, just chat with Ronnie and "Bad Asses".
没 只是跟罗尼和“大坏蛋”聊天而已
- You know them, right? - Yes, I have ever met.
-你知道他们 是么 -恩 我见过
Ladies.
女士们
Your mother wants us to get home before six o'clock. We have to go.
你妈让我们六点前回到家 我们要走了
Bye, Bro.
拜拜 哥们
Bye.
拜拜
I appreciate what you do, but do not make a mess.
我很欣赏你所做的 不过别惹出乱子
I want to avoid violence and threats.
我不想面临暴力和威胁
Handle wisely.
放聪明点
There are other ways as a defense.
有很多防卫的方法
- Wisdom what do you think? - Yeah right.
-你觉得什么是智慧 -是啊
I do not mean to offend you. But I'm not a fan of your tactics.
无意冒犯 但我不赞赏你的战术
- There is a better way to solve the problem. - Explain to us.
-有更好的方法来解决这个问题 -说说看
How did you used to be in the military, and now become flabby?
你是当过兵的人 现在怎么变的这么松懈了
Once you see what I see ...
如果你跟我见多同样的风景
... I do not want a violent manner.
我不想表现的暴力
- Jeffrey! - How are you?
-杰弗瑞 -你怎么样
Hello, boys.
嗨 各位
- I can not believe this is happening. - We'll take care of it, Jeff.
-我不敢相信这真的发生了 -我们会处理的 杰夫
I can not stop thinking about what causes it.
我一直在想原因是什么
Calm down, son. Why do not you sleep?
冷静点 兄弟 你干嘛不睡
What do you think I could sleep?
你觉得我能睡觉？
What is that?
这是什么
I am sorry. I through the plant, when parking.
对不起 停车的时候我走过草地
For some reason, maybe you do not like.
出于某些你不喜欢的原因
Only silence on the case.
一切都太安静了
I can not say anything of the things that I know.
我无法把我知道的那些准确的表达出来
It seems that the police did not handle the case, right?
看起来警察没办法处理这个案子 是么
Every effort has been deployed to arrest the perpetrators.
每一步行动都是以抓捕凶手为目的
- Nonsense! - Sorry?
-放屁 -对不起
Boss mocked as a matter of justice.
你们作为正义的代表 受到了蔑视
Listen, Mr. Vega. I fully support your actions.
听着 维加先生 我完全支持你的行动
I suggest not to be confused ...
不要疑惑
... Let us do our job, okay.
让我们专心做事 好么
Julia asked for a pillow fight with Uncle Frank. I hope you're here.
朱丽叶想跟弗兰克叔叔打枕头战 我希望你能来
- Can we talk? - Of course.
-我们能谈谈么 -当然
Sit down.
坐吧
I want to thank you for your help.
我想感谢你的帮助
It is okay.
没事
Just give them understanding.
只想让他们明白而已
I want you to take it.
我希望你能收下这个
It belonged to my father.
这是我爸爸的
Always taken during the war.
他带着它上战场
Pure titanium. As a talisman lifesavers.
纯钛 是护身符来着
You can see the bullet holes.
你还能看到单孔
- Very nice, but I can not accept it. - Please.
-很棒 但我不能收下 -请收下吧
I want to give it to you.
我想把它给你
Thank you.
谢谢
If you can ...
如果你能...
- ... May I ask you something? - Of course.
-我能问你些事么 -当然
Do you always ... be a hero?
你是...英雄么
I Have No Idea.
我不知道
I wondered what I had something that I had ...
我也想知道我到底是
- ... Or not. - Just do it.
还是不是 -放手去做吧
Be yourself.
做自己
And make the right decision.
做出正确的选择
What could be stopped ngobrolnya ...
有什么能阻止？？
... And sleep?
和睡意
4 hours 41 minutes
4小时41分
- How many times have you rubbing your nose? - I do not count them.
-你摸鼻子摸了多久了 -我没数啊
Habits of the parents of the South.
-南部父母的习惯
All Right.
好吧
I promise, if I'm out of here, I'm going to Jenny Craig (fitness).
我答应 如果我离开这 我会去找杰尼·克拉格
Password?
密码？
"Long beard"!
“长胡子”
"Moonlight"!
“月光”
It takes more pepper. Add it.
这需要更多胡椒 放多点
- All Right. - What do we have here?
-好了 -我们还有什么
Not bad. You can put more peppers. / Thank you.
还行 还能再下多点胡椒 谢谢
You mix any here, moron?
你把这里搞乱了 白痴
Who are you calling stupid, stupid?
你在叫谁白痴 你这个白痴
- Who are you? - Where is Carmen?
-你是谁 -卡门在哪
You did not answer my question. Where is Carmen?
你没回答我的问题 卡门在哪
I'm going to marry her cousin ...
我就要跟他的侄子结婚了
Damn!
该死的
Halo, 1988!
哈罗 1988
All Right. Who will die first?
好吧 谁要先受死
You like to go to hell!
给我下地狱吧
Where is Carmen?
卡门在哪
- Fuck! - All Right!
-艹 -好吧
No, no!
不 不
I'll tell you! Stop It!
我告诉你 停下
In an old building.
她在一座老房子里
I grab my wallet and car.
我去拿我的钱包和车
You'll never forgive you, asshole?
你永远不会原谅你自己的 混蛋
- But the door ...? - Get out of here.
-这个门... -离开这
Bring me Harrison.
带我去见哈里森
Enter your goal.
输入你的目标
I hope the big bearded man has a will.
我希望这个大胡子是个好人
I do not know how to get back. / What?
要怎么回退 什么
I wrote the wrong address and do not know how to remove it.
我输入了错误的地址 不知道怎么删除它
Try clicking the "delete".
试试点击“删除”
- Where is the button? - In the "keyboard".
-按钮在哪 -在“键盘”上
I do not need anymore help.
我不再需要帮助了
Thank God, we do not know where we are.
谢天谢地 我们都不知道我们在哪了
Raise your hand slowly!
慢慢举起你的手
- Wait, what? - Shut up and lift up your hands!
-等等 什么 -闭嘴 把手举起来
See you! Glad to see you guys.
再见 很高兴见到你们
I'll tell you ... this is not the safest place.
我想跟你说 这不是最安全的地方
Fuck this kid sucks!
这个该死的小孩
Just try it!
试试看
What happened?
什么事
Come on, they do not want to help us.
来吧 他们不想帮我们
Good morning, Mr. Vega.
早上好 维加先生
- Where are you taking us? - It was a surprise.
-你要带我们去哪 -这是惊喜
But I'll tell you, that ... the landscape is very special.
但是我想说...这风景真是特别呢
I'll tell you ...
我想说...
I told you not to interfere, but you do not want to listen.
我已经告诉过你别插手了 但你没听
This time you will suffer the consequences.
这次你该尝尝后果了
Listen, we will give you a last chance.
听着 我们会给你最后一次机会
Do not make me kill you, if it has been completed.
别让我杀你 如果这已经完成了
There will be no smoke without fire, bro? Bait is placed ...
无风不起浪 知道么 哥们 诱饵已经放置好了
- ... And you get caught. - You can not run away.
-...然后你就被抓了 -你跑不掉的
I'm the chief of police. I upholder of justice!
我是首席警官 我代表着正义
We will go a long way, gentlemen.
我们有一大段路要走了 先生们
You will find peace in the cemetery.
你会在墓地找到安宁的
I hope you enjoy "Bon Voyage".
希望你“旅途愉快”
Fuck you!
艹
24 seconds
24秒
- Hello?
- Wait for us at the dock at 6.
-哈罗？ -在第六码头等我们
Wife who brought the money. Alone.
让你老婆一个人带着钱来
If we look at other people there ... your daughter will die.
如果有其他人在场...你就等着给你女儿收尸吧
Wait a minute! Hello?
等等 喂
Excuse me, I'm looking for Sheriff Broussard.
打扰一下 我在找舍福瑞·布朗萨德
- He'll be back in 20 minutes. - I'll wait.
-他20分钟后回来 -我等他
You want to play canasta? (Playing cards)
你想玩牌么
The three of us.
我们三个一起
- I do not know how we get out of here. - Seize their parachutes.
-我不知道要怎么离开这 -没收他们的降落伞
Oh, shit!
哦 该死的
- Bernie, are you okay? - It feels very sick.
-伯尼 你还好么 -感觉不太好
He needs help, bro!
他需要帮忙 哥们
He had a liver transplant surgery and body rejected it.
他做过肝移植手术 现在身体产生排斥
If you do not act, he would swallow his tongue!
如果你不做点什么 他会咬断自己的舌头的
Oh, shit!
哦 艹
Come on, I need your help!
快来 我需要你的帮忙
Good evening, friends.
晚上好 我的朋友们
Great.
很好
- How do I fly? - I have watched "Top Gun" hundreds of times!
-我要怎么飞 -我看过几百遍“壮志凌云”
We need to understand how to land.
我们要先想想怎么降落
Let's see if there are manual in a drawer.
看看抽屉里有没有操作手册
Glove compartment? This is not your dad's car?
储物箱？这不是你老爸的车
I tried this.
我试过了
Hey ... hey! Gosh Vega! Do not operate any hasty!
嘿...嘿 天啊 维加 别草率行动
You're a good boy!
你是个好孩子
We're going to land this plane!
我们要降落这架飞机
I think you have to raise a little.
我觉得你要升高一点
I'm not sure at this point.
我也不太懂
- It will not work, bro. - I'm going to try a variety of ways!
-这行不懂 哥们 -我打算试试别的方法
Frank, try another, may be successful!
弗兰克 试试别的 可能会成功
- Damn! - Damn!
-该死的 -该死
Damn!
-该死
You never learn in school driving! We can not do anything!
你还没上过驾校 我们什么都做不了的
Thank you for traveling to Mexico Airlines.
感谢达成墨西哥航空
There is no signal!
没有信号了
- What would you do? - I will ask for help!
我们在某个地方的中间 离降落点至少还有70公里
We are in the middle of nowhere! At least 70 km from the settlement!
-你要干什么 -我想寻求帮助
- So, you just stay here! - You can not, bro ...
-你好好呆在哪 -你不能 哥们
What about what people say about crocodiles and werewolves?
如果别人说我们是鳄鱼和狼人怎么办
Okay, wait.
好吧 等着
Bernie, I do not have time for this nonsense. Do you want to come or stay.
伯尼 我没时间去处理这件屁事 你只能来 或者是不来
You can not do both!
不能两件事都做
What is that?
这是什么
What is this?
No matter whether you're in LA or here, all rushing somewhere.
不管你是在洛杉矶或是其他地方 我们都在做着些什么
What do we do now?
我们现在怎么做
Through the roadside.
穿过路边
I saw so many security! How do we get there?
我看到很多守卫 我们怎么去那里
Why are you always whining? Will I worked!
你怎么总是说不完 我会解决的
- What are you doing? - I lost my contact lenses.
-你在做什么 -我的隐形眼睛掉了
I found it!
我找到了
Oh, God ...
哦 我的天
Let's go.
走吧
Do not move, asshole!
别动 混蛋
I know you. You're the old fart, right!
我知道你 你就是那个大家伙 对吧
- Yes I Do. - We are the one.
-是的 -我们是一伙的
You all are amazing!
你们实在太惊人了
- Thank you, friends! - I appreciate it.
-谢谢你 兄弟 -我很欣赏
You have many fans.
你有很多粉丝
Unfortunately, I have to kill you.
不幸的是 我不得杀了你
- Please? - What Are?
-拜托 -什么
Obliterate you.
摧毁你
- Now, you will die. - Listen ...
-现在 你就要死了 -听着...
You do not need to kill two parents.
你根本不需要杀了我们四个
I'm sorry, friend. It's my job.
对不起 我的朋友 这是我的工作
Go to sleep, asshole.
长眠吧 混蛋
- What happened with wisdom, Earl? - To hell with wisdom.
-你脑子怎么了 厄尔？ -见鬼的脑子
Let us liberate my daughter!
把我女儿救出来吧
Do you have any ideas?
你有方法么
Here you are.
给你
How do we know where he is?
我们怎么知道他在哪
I think we found it.
我们会找到的
- Any suggestions? - None.
-有问题么 -没有
Let's go.
走吧
Damn, Earl!
该死的 厄尔
- Okay, it's time, folks! - You know, he punyak many events.
-好了 时间到了 伙计 -你知道的 他太会惹事了
- Dad, what are you doing here? - Are you okay?
-老爸 你在这干嘛 -你还好么
We should get going.
我们要走了
We have to go.
必须走了
Come catch this bastard.
去抓这个混蛋
Would you like a bitch?
你会像个婊子一样么
Very impressive! Drop your weapons.
真是令人印象深刻 放下你的枪
Drop your weapons!
把枪放下
- What are you doing, Jeffrey? - I know this must be confusing.
-你在干嘛 杰弗瑞 -我知道你肯定想不通
Its true that ...
事实是...
... The plan goes well before you two come.
...在你俩来之前 计划进行的很顺利
Jeffrey, if you want to cheat us, should have said from the beginning, ..
杰弗瑞 如果你想骗我们 应该一开始就跟我们说
... Before my father signed the check.
在我父亲签那张支票之前
I always liked humor.
我一直很幽默
Take his gun.
把他的枪拿下
No one will hurt her unless there is someone who wants to be a hero.
没有人想伤害她 除非某人想成为英雄
Go to another room.
去另一个房间
The Current!
现在！
You also go.
你也走
Who are you?
你是谁
You do not intend to marry her, right?
你根本没想跟她结婚 对吧
She was a remarkable woman, if the situation is different ... who knows ...
她是个非凡的女人 如果境地不同...谁知道呢...
But this is a business opportunity that will be shared with my cousin.
但这是个能跟我的侄子一起分享的商业机遇
Cousin? Police Chief Broussard?
侄子？首席警官布罗萨德？
And.
也是同谋
You're right, Mr. Vega.
是的 维加先生
Leave my daughter with us. I gave the ransom.
把我女儿还给我 我把赎金给你
I wish I could trust you.
我很想相信你
Unfortunately I do not believe you. We have big plans for Carmen.
可是我不信你 我们为卡门准备了一个大计划
Son of a bitch!
混蛋
Calm down, Earl.
冷静 厄尔
Later they also arrested.
他们等下会被逮捕的
I doubt Mr. Vega.
我很怀疑啊 维加先生
It's late for everything.
所有的一切都不会发生
Farewell good.
再见了
Lucas!
卢卡斯
Let's go.
我们走
Oh, damn!
噢 该死的
I think I'm going to eat barbecue tonight ...
我今晚想吃烧烤
- ... Sprinkled with mayonaise ... - Oh, this bond is very strong!
-...撒上美乃滋 -哦 这个骨头很强壮
Come On! We still have something in this regard.
来吧 我们还有一些事没处理呢
My hands are tied!
我的手被绑住了
We got stuck. Can not get out of here.
我们被困住了 出不去了
"Let us go then Louisiana!"
“我们去路易桑那吧”
"Little getaway to relax!"
“去放放松”
- You blame me, right? - Of course your fault!
-你在怪我 是么 -当然是你的错
Can not you just once in charge?
就不能是你的错么
If it were not for you, we would not be here! / Enough!
如果不是为了你 我们才不会在这里 够了
Can not you at least die in peace?
你就不能安静的走么
Sorry, pal.
对不起 爸爸
It's a nice ride.
真是愉快的旅程
- Yes it is. - Yes I Do!
-是的 -我也觉得
- Do you need a ride? - Of course!
-你想去兜风么 -当然
Let's go!
走吧
I feel embarrassed! You're my white child!
我觉得很尴尬 你是我的孩子啊
Save our lives!
我救了你们
How did you know we were here?
你怎么知道我们在那
I Have No Idea! I hid in the trunk.
我没有办法 只能躲在卡车里
Remains exactly 22 minutes to arrive, before your mother made the exchange.
在你妈来交易之前 我们还有22分钟离开
22 minutes? From this place at least 45 minutes!
22分钟 离开这里至少要45分钟吧
Hit the gas, kid!
大踩油门 孩子
They have a team!
他们有人
- We need help! - Ronald, borrow your phone!
-我们需要援助 -罗纳德 带上你的手机
- Jeffrey? - Hello, madam.
-杰弗瑞？ -哈罗 女士
I know you would not expect.
我知道你肯定想不到
Give the money and I will hand over Carmen.
给我钱 然后我给你们卡门
You ... you! Hell, dirty pig!
你...你 见鬼 你这肮脏的猪头
- Give me the money! - Fuck you.
-把钱给我 -艹
I admire your courage, but it is not needed here.
我欣赏你的勇气 但是在这里派不上用场
I will not give you anything, until you submit Carmen.
你把卡门给我 不然我什么都不会给你的
As you wish.
如你所想
Now, I'm going to kick your ass.
现在 我要揍扁你
Come on dear.
走吧 亲爱的
It's you!
是你
Well done, dear!
好了 亲爱的
The little boy saved! Finally, I could see!
终于救了她的 我就知道
Louisiana police finally arrived!
路易桑那的警察终于到了
Raise your hands!
举起你的手
Oh gosh! Jeffrey!
天哪 杰弗瑞
How could this happen?
怎么能发生这样的事呢
Son of a bitch!
混蛋
I think it is mine.
这是我的
Mr. Vega!
维加先生
You almost managed to mess it all up!
你几乎搞砸了这一切
Now, you all must die.
现在 你们都要去死
I start with you.
从你开始
Asshole fucking.
混蛋
Do not move!
别动
Drop the gun, Broussard!
放下枪 布罗萨德
What are you doing here?
你在干什么
Has ended, drop the gun!
一切都结束了 把枪放下
You're dealing with a ...
你是在跟...
... Which is much larger. If I were you ...
...一个更危险的人玩火 如果我是你...
... I'm going home.
...我就乖乖回家
Take away the children.
把孩子带走
Drop the gun, Broussard!
放下枪 布罗萨德
Raise your hands! The Current!
举起你的手 现在!
Do not act as a brave boy!
别逞能了
We recommend that you retreat!
我劝你退下
Because I'm going to shoot him.
因为我要杀了他
Back Off!
退后
Stay back!
You shot me!
你射中了我！
- Frank, are you okay? - Yes I Do.
-弗兰克 你还好么 -恩
Damn, bag it to save your life, Frank!
该死的 把伤口包扎下 这能救你的命 弗兰克
This clock!
这个时钟
An hour to save your life.
只剩一小时来救你命了
Hey, "Green Machine" do you have anything in your pocket?
嘿 “绿色机器” 你口袋里有东西么
Remains lie, motherfucker!
躺着别动 混蛋
Yah..kami now want to say goodbye.
呀..卡门现在要跟你们说再见啦
Come on, are you sure you will not stay a day longer? / I feel bad!
来吧 你确定你不再多留一天？我感觉很糟
We would like to, but Bernie had to go to the doctor tomorrow morning.
我们也想 不过伯尼明天早上要去看医生
Okay, then. Give me a hug!
那好吧 抱一个
You do not know how I'm very grateful. Many thanks!
你不知道我有多感谢你 非常感谢
- It's okay. - Yes I Do.
-别客气 -我也很感谢
Who needs a man when you two?
谁需要一个男人？
You are always welcome here!
欢迎你们随时来这
There are five minutes before you go. Can I talk to you?
还剩五分钟就要走了  我能跟你说句话么
Thank you from the bottom of heart.
我全身心的感谢你
My son has returned.
我的儿子回来了
Words not enough just to thank you.
我的感谢已无法用言语表达了
But you gave me something else. For the first time in 30 years ...
你也给了我其他的东西啦 30年来第一次...
... 30 years! I feel alive again!
30年来 我感觉又活过来了
So, I found myself true.
我找到了真正的自己
I want to go back to dispense justice in places completely disappeared.
我想去正义消失的地方 维持正义
And I want to do with you.
我想跟你一起
Accept ... as the "Three old fart" ...
好的 就像打人的
... Who kick ass.
“三个老家伙”
Sounds great, Earl, but ...
听起来不错啊 但是 厄尔...
- ... Bernie has other responsibilities. - Frank, I know about the library.
-伯尼有其他的责任 -弗兰克 我知道图书馆的事
Bernie has a liquor store. Do not make you stop.
伯尼有一间白酒店 别让自己停步
I want to make as easy as possible.
我想做的尽可能简单点
I will pay for the entire operation.
我会为整场手术买单的
And you will be paid.
而你也会有收获的
You do not have to worry about finances, especially to buy drugs.
你不用担心钱的问题 特别是买药的钱
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
Serious liver transplantation.
跟手术一样真
What do you think, my friend?
你觉得呢 伙计
What is ready to "cleanse" the country?
什么时候开始“净化”城市呢
Coming soon ...
很快了...
...Bad Asses di Bangkok.
大坏蛋要到曼谷啦
Hey, Bernie! You can be more than you are looking for!
嘿 伯尼 你能成为更好的自己
I tell you, I loved it.
跟你说哦 我喜欢这样
And me too!
我也是
Sorry, sir. You should go back to your seat.
不好意思 先生 请回到您自己的座位上
零点字幕组翻译媛，转载请保留此信息